That's interesting advice,
coming from a slave owner.
Men have enslaved each other...
since they invented gods
to forgive them for doing it.
I've seen Jews build Egypt's glory.
Seen Christians...
thrown to lions with my own eyes.
And I've seen Africans
sell their own kind to Europeans.
May I share one of the revelations
of my 5,000 years?
We're all slaves to something.
I, to eternity.
You, to your convictions.
Others, to the color of their skin.
All I ever wanted...
was to see my kind
granted their rightful place.
But there are those of us,
those like your friend Henry...
who enjoy living in the dark.
And as you're doubtless aware...
I cannot personally destroy him,
nor he I.
You, Mr. Lincoln...
you could eliminate those
last pockets of resistance...
beginning with Henry Sturges himself.
All I ask...
is for you to break your chains.
Kill your master.
Be free.
And if I refuse?
Then you go on your merry way.
After I make you one of us, and...
spoon-feed you your friend.
Now, a simple "yes" or "no"
will suffice.
Kill Henry...
save your friend.
Feel free to take your time to decide.
Five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
Come on!
This way.
Miss Tubman, Miss Tubman.
We've been waiting for you.
Come quickly.