l have sailed the world
Beheld its wonders
From the Dardanelles
To the mountains of Peru
But there's no place like London
No, there's no place like London
Mr. Todd?
You are young
Life has been kind to you
You will learn
There's a hole in the world
like a great black pit
And the vermin of the world inhabit it
And its morals aren't worth
what a pig could spit
And it goes by the name of London
At the top of the hole
sit a privileged few
Making mock of the vermin
in the lower zoo
Turning beauty into filth and greed
l too have sailed the world
and seen its wonders
For the cruelty of men
is as wondrous as Peru
But there's no place like London
ls everything all right, Mr. Todd?
l beg your indulgence, Anthony.
My mind is far from easy.
ln these once familiar streets
l feel shadows everywhere.
Shadows?
Ghosts.
There was a barber and his wife
And she was beautiful